Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(Episode 2)
Your Highness.
My face.
You can humiliate Lu Zhao...
all you want.
But you can't kill her.
Xue Er.
In a few days,
Lu Zhao will turn 18 years old.
Only after the birthday banquet...
will she have the right...
to take over all the Lu family assets...
from the head of the Lu Clan.
If you kill her...
before that happens,
you'll ruin my plan.
Your Highness.
I didn't want to kill her.
I just drugged her.
I wanted to get rid of this child for you.
I don't care how you usually spoil or pamper her.
She can have the title of your wife and have the utmost honor.
I don't care about any of that.
But the one thing I can't bear...
is to see you have a child with another woman.
Why should she get to do that?
Why?
- Why? - Xue Er.
Come on.
Get up.
I don't want to have a child...
with another woman either.
You're the only one...
who shall bear my child.
But...
Right now,
I haven't gotten what I wanted yet.
I still need to use this child...
to control the Lu family.
You...
are my one and only wife.
Beg me.
Tonight,
let's have a child.
My dear brother-in-law.
It's my fault.
Don't be angry.
It's snowing outside.
Please, Xian.
Carry me back.
Jin Lin.
Yes.
As usual,
keep watch for me here.
My child.
Your Highness.
I just had a dream.
I dreamed that we lost our child.
I was covered in blood,
lying in the snow.
I'm so scared right now.
Your Highness.
Go with me to Fanyin Temple tomorrow.
Let's pray for our child.
Your Highness.
Why aren't you saying anything?
No.
You're not His Highness.
Who are you?
Lu Zhao.
It's me.
I had urgent business to attend to.
I just went to take care of it.
I picked up some cold energy...
and I didn't want you to get cold,
so I changed my clothes.
You didn't say anything just now.
I thought it was someone else lying next to me.
You scared me.
Lu Zhao.
You're pregnant now.
It's normal that you'll overthink things.
Get some rest.
Tomorrow,
I'll go to the temple with you...
to pray for our child.
All right?
Okay.
Step back!
Don't come any closer.
Don't move!
He's your master's twin brother.
If you don't want him to die here,
put down your weapons!
Let me go!
Put down your weapons.
Step back.
You're the leader of the Xuntian Sect,
Xiao Jin Yu.
Xiao Jin Yu!
You people pushed me over the edge.
Don't blame me for not showing you mercy.
You're about to die.
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing because you don't know the Xuntian Sect at all.
You don't know my sister either.
If I weren't afraid you'd blow yourself up,
you'd never have caught me.
Idiot.
Who did you sell your weapons to?
I'd rather die than betray my boss.
You're so righteous.
In that case,
when I stick this into your eyeball later,
you must hang in there.
Don't! I'll tell you.
It's the guard of the Prince of Chu's manor, Jin Lin.
He's very cautious.
A different person comes every time.
I only found out by chance.
There's indeed something fishy about the Prince of Chu.
You're really cruel.
You almost killed me too.
You have the Golden Silkworm.
You can't feel pain, and you're immune to poison.
What are you afraid of?
Look. You're not dead, right?
I...
The Prince of Chu is at Fanyin Temple...
praying with the Princess of Chu.
I have to go there.
You...
should go back and treat your wounds when you can move.
I'm leaving.
Come back soon.
Be careful, Lu Zhao.
Xue Er.
It's so cold today,
yet you came to pray for my child with me.
Thank you so much.
What are you saying?
The Prince of Chu's future son is so precious.
Of course, I have to pray for him with you.
I heard that wishes come true at Fanyin Temple.
If you write down your wishes...
and hang them on the tree,
they will come true.
Lu Zhao.
You can't see well. I'll write it for you.
What do you want to write?
I don't have much to ask for.
I just want my child...
to come to this world safely.
I want his life to be smooth sailing.
All right.
- Wait for me. - Okay.
Lu Zhao.
Here.
I've finished writing it.
Your Highness, take a look.
What do you think?
(Die a horrible death)
It's good.
Here.
Lu Zhao.
Take the amulet...
and kowtow to Buddha.
Remember.
You have to be sincere...
for the Buddha to hear your prayers.
Okay.
Well, Lu Zhao,
I'll let you pray here quietly.
I won't disturb you.
Okay.
Lu Zhao.
I'm going to make an offering to the temple...
to bring good blessings to our child.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I pray to the Buddha...
that my child will be born safely.
I pray...
that my child will always be safe.
Do you really think...
that praying to the Buddha...
will allow your child to be born safely?
Princess of Chu.
Who are you?
You know I'm praying for my child,
yet you're speaking rudely in front of Buddha.
Aren't you afraid of being punished?
I'm the leader of the Xuntian Sect,
Xiao Jin Yu.
I've committed many murders in my life,
so I'm not afraid of the gods or Buddha.
I've long heard that Master Xiao...
has been working for His Majesty.
You've never interfered with the Prince of Chu.
Now, you've barged into this temple...
and said these things to me.
What's your motive?
You're quite smart.
Yet, why are you blinded...
by the Prince of Chu?
You don't see the danger before you.
Master Xiao.
I've been blind for years.
One does not have to be blinded to be ignorant.
What one should fear is not blindness of the eyes,
but blindness of the heart.
You...
What do you mean by that?
Your cousin, Liu Ying Xue,
secretly bought a poison...
that can blind people four years ago.
And your eyes...
also went blind four years ago.
Take a guess.
Was it a coincidence?
Or was it someone's doing?
The Xuntian Sect is ruthless.
Everyone knows it.
I don't know you at all.
I won't believe a word you say.
You don't believe me?
The Prince of Chu and that Liu Ying Xue...
are fooling around in the room in the backyard right now.
You can verify it yourself.
Master Xiao.
You don't have to fool me.
I won't doubt my loved ones...
just because of what you said.
Please leave.
Your loved ones?
Your Prince of Chu never thought...
of keeping this child of yours.
And he never thought...
of keeping you alive.
If you don't believe me,
you can show this amulet...
to others.
What exactly did Liu Ying Xue...
write on it?
That's enough!
What exactly do you want?
I want to work with you.
I'll help you...
see their true colors.
You...
can be my spy in the Prince of Chu's manor.
This is the Xuntian Sect's secret medicine.
It can not only cure your blindness...
but also make you immune to poison for three days.
Take it.
Go and see for yourself...
what lies and torment...
you've been living in?
Once you see the truth and come around,
you can come find me at the Xuntian Sect anytime.
Take it.
This orchid jade pendant is our token.
In exchange,
I'll help you take revenge.
Your Highness.
What is it?
The arms trafficker who secretly manufactures weapons for us...
was killed on his way here.
What happened?
It was the Xuntian Sect.
They might have their eyes on us now.
Your Highness, please leave this place now.
Xiao Jin Yu.
Ms. Lu Zhao.
Let me help you get to bed.
Bao Qin.
Help me take a look.
What is written on this amulet?
(Die a horrible death)
Ms. Lu Zhao, where did you find this evil thing?
What's the matter?
This is clearly a prayer amulet,
but it's written with cursed red ink.
It even says,
"Die a horrible death."
This is an ominous item.
Throw it away now.
Wait.
Give it to me.
Bao Qin.
Get someone to test this.
Find out what this pill does.
Where did you get this pill?
You mustn't take random medicine.
It's better to ask His Highness...
to summon the physician here.
No.
His Highness mustn't know about this.
Go now.
All right.
I'll do as you wish.
Go now.